Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪
[The Sparrow's Gambit]
[مناورة العصفور]
[Episode 20]
[الحلقة 20]
Can't sleep?
لا تستطيع النوم؟
Not a wink.
لا غمزة.
Worried about Wan'er?
هل أنت قلق بشأن وان إير؟
The one behind this is cruel.
الذي وراء هذا قاسي.
Now that it's blown up like this,
الآن وقد تم تفجيره بهذا الشكل،
they'll silence Wan'er to shut it down.
سيسكتون وان إير لإيقافه.
I don't know what to do anymore.
لا أعرف ماذا أفعل بعد الآن.
When this is all over,
عندما ينتهي كل هذا،
I'll make you dumplings myself.
سأصنع لك الزلابية بنفسي.
Okay.
تمام.
Karma!
كارما!
It's all karma.
إنها كلها كارما.
Karma.
كارما.
Karma...
كارما...
Wenbin,
وينبين،
you're back.
لقد عدت.
Look at my face.
أنظر إلى وجهي.
Pretty?
جميل؟
Yeah.
نعم.
And him.
وهو.
He's back.
لقد عاد.
And him...
وهو...
Yeah...
نعم...
Who?
من؟
Who is he?
من هو؟
He's...
إنه...
He...
هو...
Miss Liu,
السيدة ليو،
you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Wang Wan'er lost it.
وانغ وان إير فقدتها.
She almost hurt you.
لقد كادت أن تؤذيك.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Thank you, sir.
شكرا لك سيدي.
Anyone who touches opium
كل من يلمس الأفيون
is already dead.
لقد مات بالفعل.
She had it coming.
لقد كان يستحق ذلك.
Don't let it trouble you, Miss Liu.
لا تدعي الأمر يزعجك، يا آنسة ليو.
Now you're dead,
الآن أنت ميت
and no one can ever threaten me
ولا يمكن لأحد أن يهددني أبدًا
with the opium trade again.
مع تجارة الأفيون مرة أخرى.
[Orphanage]
[دار الأيتام]
He...
هو...
Wang Penghui's dead.
مات وانغ بينغوي.
Wang Wan'er's dead.
وانغ وان إير ماتت.
The Lins are avenged.
تم الانتقام للينس.
It should all be over now.
يجب أن يكون كل شيء قد انتهى الآن.
Is it really over?
هل انتهى الأمر حقا؟
The baby Wan'er was carrying
الطفل وان إير كان يحمل
wasn't your father's.
لم يكن لوالدك.
How did he find out about her
كيف عرف عنها؟
and bring her back?
وأعيدها؟
That shot in the hospital,
تلك اللقطة في المستشفى،
was it really to save me?
هل كان ذلك حقا لإنقاذي؟
So you suspect my father?
هل تشك في والدي؟
Wan'er left me this note.
لقد ترك لي وانر هذه المذكرة.
The child was Mr. Li's.
وكان الطفل للسيد لي.
Mr. Li's dead.
السيد لي مات.
Wang Wan'er, too.
وانغ وان إير أيضًا.
Don't you have any doubts at all?
هل ليس لديك أي شك على الإطلاق؟
Or you turn a blind eye,
أو تغض الطرف،
just because he's your father?
فقط لأنه والدك؟
I'm not stopping you from digging.
أنا لا أمنعك من الحفر.
But Wang Wan'er never said
ولكن وانغ وان إير لم تقل ذلك أبدًا
who was behind it.
من كان وراء ذلك؟
Why would she tell you?
لماذا تريد أن تخبرك؟
After everything she did,
بعد كل ما فعلته،
don't you see?
ألا ترى؟
She was trying to drive us apart.
لقد كانت تحاول التفريق بيننا.
and keep us from being together
وتمنعنا من أن نكون معًا
Why believe her over me?
لماذا أصدقها أكثر مني؟
So tell me...
فأخبرني...
What am I to you?
ماذا أنا بالنسبة لك؟
[The Paramount]
[الباراماونت]
Wang Wan'er's dead.
وانغ وان إير ماتت.
The evidence at the orphanage
الأدلة في دار الأيتام
will be destroyed, too.
سيتم تدميرها أيضا.
You're going, right? Let me help.
أنت ذاهب، صحيح؟ دعني أساعدك.
I know you can fight,
أنا أعلم أنك قادر على القتال،
but having backup
ولكن لدي نسخة احتياطية
beats going in solo.
ضربات تسير منفردة.
I'll just be the driver.
سأكون فقط السائق.
All I want is the exclusive.
كل ما أريده هو الحصري.
Deal then?
صفقة إذن؟
I'll pick you up tonight.
سألتقطك الليلة.
Don't stand me up!
لا تقفني!
Rumeng,
رومينج،
if my father
إذا كان والدي
did all this,
فعلت كل هذا،
I won't cover for him.
لن اغطي عليه
I want to face it with you.
أريد أن أواجه الأمر معك.
Get in.
أدخل.
Wenbin's investigating there, too.
وينبين يحقق هناك أيضًا.
Same direction.
نفس الإتجاه.
We go together.
نحن نذهب معا.
What kind of driving is that?
ما هذا النوع من القيادة؟
My bad.
خطئي.
[Sunshine Orphanage] Rumeng!
[دار أيتام الشمس] رومينج!
Rumeng.
رومينج.
Put this on.
ضع هذا.
Be careful.
احرص.
Over here!
هنا!
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Show yourself!
اظهر نفسك!
You two, go! Now!
أنتما الاثنان، اذهبا الآن!
Move!
يتحرك!
Go!
يذهب!
Who's that?
من هو الذي؟
Freeze!
تجميد!
Move! Now!
تحرك! الآن!
Su Zhengzhi,
سو تشنغزي,
thought you'd run?
هل فكرت في الركض؟
Chen Shangfu!
تشن شانغفو!
Where's my son?
أين ابني؟
He's doing fine.
إنه بخير.
He's the Young Marshal now.
إنه المارشال الشاب الآن.
I raised him, watched him grow.
لقد ربيته، وشاهدته يكبر.
Grew quite fond of him.
لقد أحببته كثيرًا.
One day, he'll take over Song City
في يوم من الأيام، سوف يستولي على مدينة سونغ
and our business.
وأعمالنا.
Chen Shangfu!
تشن شانغفو!
You monster!
أيها الوحش!
You stole my wife,
لقد سرقت زوجتي
took my boy,
أخذت ابني
even forced me to make that poison,
حتى أجبروني على صنع هذا السم،
and you want Jinmo in this filth too?
وتريد جينمو في هذه القذارة أيضًا؟
Chen Shangfu, I'm killing you!
تشن شانغفو، أنا أقتلك!
Kill...
قتل...
Chen Shangfu,
تشن شانغفو،
I'll never let Jinmo
لن اسمح لجينمو أبدًا
become a devil like you.
أصبح شيطانًا مثلك.
He's Chen Wenbin now.
إنه تشين وينبين الآن.
He's my son.
إنه ابني
Do as you're told. Make the opium.
افعل كما أُمرت. اصنع الأفيون.
And I will ensure he becomes powerful and admired.
وسوف أتأكد من أنه يصبح قويًا ومحبوبًا.
What's wrong with that?
ما الخطأ في ذلك؟
Chen Shangfu!
تشن شانغفو!
I'm gonna kill you!
سأقتلك!
Take him away!
خذه بعيدا!
Chen Shangfu!
تشن شانغفو!
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪Magnolia petals fly across the sky♪
♪بتلات الماغنوليا تطير عبر السماء♪
♪Spring and autumn come and go♪
♪الربيع والخريف يأتيان ويذهبان♪
♪People gather and part♪
♪يتجمع الناس ويفترقون♪
♪How brave can one be with no regrets?♪
♪كيف يمكن للإنسان أن يكون شجاعًا دون أن يشعر بالندم؟♪
♪I will paint love and hate in the sky♪
♪سأرسم الحب والكراهية في السماء♪
♪Engraving my love for you♪
♪نقش حبي لك♪
♪I roam through this chaotic world♪
♪أتجول في هذا العالم الفوضوي♪
♪Who will guard me for life?♪
♪من سيحرسني طيلة حياتي؟♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪